It's Neferpitou.
[both gasp]
That is the name
the Queen bestowed upon me.
From now on, you can call me Neferpitou.
[opening theme music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[singer singing in English]
LIGHT X AND X DARK
[Peggy] Attention squadron leaders
and officers.
Attention squadron leaders and officers.
Commander Neferpitou will be holding
a conferment ceremony in hall one
and, of course, you're all invited.
[laughs, knuckles cracking]
[Peggy] A brief moment of suffering,
the Chimera Ant nest
is almost certainly up ahead.
Man, that's amazing.
He tracked him this whole time
and never lost them once.
He said that his En covers
a radius of 45 meters.
I've heard that the ones called
Nen masters can handle around 50 meters.
Stronger than a master, huh?
He must be the real deal, I guess.
Yeah, he's the first pro we've met.
Well, at least like this.
but we really only knew him
as another player in a game.
And Bisky was an incredible hunter,
but to us…
[Killua] And then there was
the first person to teach us about Nen.
[Gon] Master Wing,
our Nen master and savior.
And now that I think about it,
we always meet people
when we need them the most.
It's them, all these people we've met,
who have made us stronger.
-I guess Razor counts too, huh?
-Yeah.
It's pretty obvious to me that Ging really
did create Greed Island to train you.
I don't know if Ging could have predicted
what was gonna happen when we met Kite,
And he definitely knew you'd follow him,
that much I'm sure of.
You might be right but this is
a pretty brutal place for training.
And that is exactly the reason why
I keep asking you if your resolve is firm.
[both gasp]
[Kite] I agree that, like you mentioned,
Ging probably did have
certain expectations
when he sent you here to meet with me.
That being said,
I have no intention of training
the two of you during this journey.
I only brought you along
because I thought you might be useful.
From here on,
it all comes down to your resolve.
If it's strong, you'll develop your Nen
and improve through combat.
We're professional hunters, after all.
And as you're aware,
those who call themselves hunters
must get their prey.
[both gasp]
For those of our profession,
that's the first commandment.
We stay on the hunt no matter what.
It's a battle of resolve.
and this often means the loser's death.
Improving your Nen is important, sure,
but to be a successful hunter,
you must understand your enemy
as well as yourself.
Wait, I get it.
That must be why you hit me
when I met you a long time ago, right?
If you see that mark then you stay away,
even the animals know that much.
[gasps softly]
That was the rule of the forest, it was,
wasn't it?
You were teaching me the rules
in Ging's place.
[Kite] Oh, that's right,
I just remembered.
-It's a hunter's license.
-But whose?
[Kite] It's Ging's.
Huh? It's Ging's?
Just think back to my final test.
Remember what it was?
He told me I was supposed to use it
to find him someday.
No, I'd actually forgotten I had it.
[boys gasp]
Gon, you said you were gonna find Ging
on your own, didn't you?
Uh…
[grunts softly]
Then you have to do
what you said you would.
Once I'm done,
I'll find Ging and give this back to him.
We don't wanna lose the trail.
[Rammot grunts]
[Kite] A monster!
What is this? I don't believe it.
[Gon] What's wrong, Kite?
-[Kite] Gon, Killua, run.
-[boys] Huh?
I said, go! Get out of here right now!
I found you.
Get away!
[both gasp]
[both grunting]
[breath trembling]
[yelling]
[Kite] Idiot!
[soft thud]
Wise decision, Killua.
Now take Gon and get out of here.
[cackling] You're in for it now,
you know that?
[Killua] We were too complacent
and overconfident.
[imperceptible]
[Killua] We were both worth
less than a one-armed Kite,
that was his assessment.
That's the reality.
If Kite had been alone,
this probably wouldn't have happened.
[grunts]
Damn it, we were fools.
Hey.
Is that…
[panting]
[breathing heavily]
[dialing]
[line ringing]
Hey, what the hell
do you think you're doing?
And we're bringing reinforcements.
-[vehicle approaching]
-Huh?
[gasps]
[Killua] Chairman Netero.
What the hell is this? They're just kids.
You got burned real bad because
you thought this was gonna be a game.
That isn't very nice.
So, was your adversary that formidable?
One of them could use Nen.
Of all the aura I've encountered,
this one was the worst.
You guys are unbelievably strong.
And still, I don't think
even you could take him.
[scoffs] People overrate things
that they can't understand,
We'll take it from here.
You just go to bed and get some rest.
[laughing]
How was that just now different
from what I said? Come on, Knov.
[Knov scoffs]
well, it just shows
you're missing the whole point.
In most cases, you don't know
what your opponent's abilities are.
And when you're in a fight like that,
All of a sudden,
having more or less aura
than the other guy
isn't really much of an excuse.
Plus, the battle can turn quickly
and at any time.
That's the essence of Nen combat.
Still, no matter what,
You're worse than a loser.
No, he's not. He tried to attack,
so I used force to stop him.
I didn't have time to hold back,
so I don't know when he'll wake up.
[laughs]
Sounds like the other kid's got
a lot more of a future.
Yet it seems to be true,
and therefore, we must attempt
to keep the casualties to a minimum.
If we send in fighters
who aren't strong enough,
[Netero] We have already placed
two assassins in the nearest city.
take them down and come find us.
We don't need just any help…
only the strong.
WILL YOU FIGHT OR NOT?
You're worse than a loser.
Well, because you knocked me out.
It was you, right?
I mean, if I'd lost control back there,
I would have gotten in the way.
And if I had,
all three of us would have died.
-Kite is still alive.
-[gasps]
He would never be beaten,
not by something like that.
just trying to move is pretty hard on him,
so he's hiding.
So now, we get strong and we find him.
We're gonna go save Kite.
-Let's go.
-[bird tweeting]
[Killua] We've gotta get stronger.
[Colt] Prepare a freezing chamber
in the fortress.
Make it large enough to store
more than a hundred humans.
[Neferpitou] To ensure that
my collection doesn't rot.
[upbeat music playing]
[Gon] Next time, Promise and Reunion.
[Gon snores]
It just has to be Killua.
[Killua] Yeah, okay. Just stay asleep.